contentmart.in 2015-07-05

# Privacy Policy | ContentMart

Contentmart.in is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our websites, as well as our members and partners. Contentmart.in has established this Privacy Policy to explain what information we collect through these websites and how it is used.

In this policy, "Contentmart.in" refers to staff, board members, cooperating attorneys, interns, volunteers, and consultants of Contentmart.in, all of whom are bound by law or contract to keep information they receive as part of their work for Contentmart.in confidential.

Contentmart.in does not sell or rent personally identifiable member, customer or employee information under any circumstances, and we do not share information without prior consent except as compelled by law. (See discussion below.)

#### Information Gathered by Contentmart.in Site

We collect information from you when you sign up with our site. When you sign up with our site, you may provide us with two types of information: 

(1) Personally identifiable information that you knowingly choose to disclose, which is collected on an individual basis, and 

(2) General user information that does not contain personally identifiable information, which is collected on an aggregate basis as you browse the site. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with requested information, you may not be able to access all of our site's content or services.

#### Contentmart.in's Use of Information

Contentmart.in sees it as its mission to protect privacy, defend freedom, and protect your rights in the digital world. We are your friends. If you invite another person to join Contentmart.in, we will ask for that person's name and online contact information. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that he or she has been invited to join Contentmart.in.

If you provide information for publication, such as writing a review or submitting other editorial content, we will publicly credit you for this work.

We may run surveys, contests, or similar activities through this site. Such information will be used for the purposes for which it was collected.

We look at technical information to diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Contentmart.in site.

#### Personally Identifiable Information You Choose to Provide

We may ask for certain personal information from you for the purpose of providing to you content and/or services that you request. For example, if you indicate an interest in receiving press releases about Contentmart.in, you are asked to submit your name and e-mail address, which we retain on file, so that we may send you the information that you requested. If you indicate on our E-mail Alert registration form that you are a member of the press, we may also send you information regarding our business. We also request your name and e-mail address each time you contact us by clicking on the "Contact Us" link. We may retain a record of users who have contacted us in order to respond properly to questions or concerns and for purposes of future communications.

#### Third-Party Service Providers

Portions of the Contentmart.in site may be operated by a third-party service provider ("Provider"). Provider may place cookies on your computer in order to store information, such as items placed in your shopping cart, or storing your account login when using the Affiliate Center. Provider logs standard technical information, such as the numerical Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site.

Our Provider also stores and organizes the personal information collected through this site on our behalf. The information remains under our control, and our agreement with Provider requires the information to be kept confidential and disclosed only to Provider's employees who require such access in the course of their assigned duties. Provider has however, not agreed to cooperate with Contentmart.in in seeking a protective order, if necessary, to protect this information from legal process. We will seek to accomplish this in all cases, but this cannot be guaranteed. Contentmart.in may change providers from time to time, and will transfer stored information to the new provider subject to similar restrictions.

Contentmart.in's search engine functionality is currently operated in house. All search queries may be retained for analysis and will always be access on an anonymous basis. Contentmart.in may however change the search engine provider from time to time.

From time to time, Contentmart.in may work with third-party consultants or other service providers who may have access to personally identifiable information. In such cases, we will restrict their use of personally identifiable information in accordance with their assigned tasks and subject to the limitations of this privacy policy.

Contentmart.in's site provides links to a wide variety of third-party websites. Contentmart.in is not responsible for, and does not have any control over, the privacy practices or the content of such third parties. We encourage users to read the privacy policies of any website visited.

#### Disclosure of Your Information

While Contentmart.in endeavors to provide the highest level of protection for your information, we may disclose personally identifiable information about you to third parties in limited circumstance, including: (1) with your consent; or (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, such as pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order.

If we are required by law to disclose the information that you have submitted, we will attempt to provide you with notice (unless we are prohibited) that a request for your information has been made in order to give you an opportunity to object to the disclosure. We will attempt to provide this notice by email, if you have given us an email address or by postal mail if you have entered a postal address. If you do not challenge the disclosure request, we may be legally required to turn over your information.

In addition, we will independently object to requests for access to information about users of our site that we believe to be improper.

#### Updating or Removing Your Information

You may choose to correct, update, or delete the membership information you have submitted to us by sending an email requesting changes to support @ Contentmart.in. Furthermore, if we inadvertently collect more personal information than intended, we endeavor to delete the extraneous information. However, please understand that deleted information may continue to persist on back-up media.

#### Changes to Our Policies

Contentmart.in's Privacy Policy may change from time to time. However, any revised privacy policy will be consistent with Contentmart.in's stance on privacy issues. If we make any substantive changes to our policies, we will place notice on Contentmart.in and post notice of changes on this page.

#### Security

Contentmart.in employs industry standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Information submitted through the online payment system processes is encrypted through a Secured Socket Layer (SSL) connections, which protects the information in transit.

Although we make good faith efforts to store information collected by Contentmart.in in a secure operating environment, we cannot guarantee complete security. Information collected by Contentmart.in will be maintained for a length of time appropriate to our needs. However, we generally do not retain credit card information unless you choose to have us do so.

#### Revision Date

This Privacy Statement was last revised in August, 2014.
